var questions = [{
	"question": "What is the maximum possible length of an identifier?",
	"option1": "31 characters",
	"option2": "63 characters",
	"option3": "79 characters",
	"option4": "none of the mentioned",
	"answer": "4"
},
{
	"question": "Which of the following is not a keyword?",
	"option1": "eval",
	"option2": "assert",
	"option3": "nonlocal",
	"option4": "pass",
	"answer": "1"
},
{
	"question": ">>>max(what are you)",
	"option1": "error",
	"option2": "u",
	"option3": "t",
	"option4": "y",
	"answer": "4"
},
{
	"question": "Suppose d = {“john”:40, “peter”:45}. To obtain the number of entries in dictionary which command do we use?",
	"option1": "d.size()",
	"option2": "len(d)",
	"option3": "size(d)",
	"option4": "d.len()",
	"answer": "2"
},
{
	"question": "The one’s complement of 110010101 is:",
	"option1": "001101010",
	"option2": "110010101",
	"option3": "001101011",
	"option4": "110010100",
	"answer": "1"
},
{
	"question": "Suppose list1 = [0.5 * x for x in range(0, 4)], list1 is:",
	"option1": "[0, 1, 2, 3]",
	"option2": "[0, 1, 2, 3, 4]",
	"option3": "[0.0, 0.5, 1.0, 1.5]",
	"option4": "[0.0, 0.5, 1.0, 1.5, 2.0]",
	"answer": "3"
},
{
	"question": "To add a new element to a list we use which command?",
	"option1": "list1.add(5)",
	"option2": "list1.append(5)",
	"option3": "list1.addLast(5)",
	"option4": "list1.addEnd(5)",
	"answer": "2"
},
{
	"question": "Suppose list1 is [3, 4, 5, 20, 5], what is list1.index(5)?",
	"option1": "0",
	"option2": "1",
	"option3": "4",
	"option4": "2",
	"answer": "4"
},
{
	"question": "Suppose list1 is [3, 4, 5, 20, 5, 25, 1, 3], what is list1.count(5)?",
	"option1": "3",
	"option2": "4",
	"option3": "2",
	"option4": "7",
	"answer": "3"
},
{
	"question": ". The assignment of more than one function to a particular operator is _______",
	"option1": "Operator over-assignment",
	"option2": "Operator overriding",
	"option3": "Operator overloading",
	"option4": "Operator instance",
	"answer": "3"
},
]